Richard Aspinall

Technical Customer Experience Specialist



EXPERIENCE

Slack — Platform Support

JULY 2020 - PRESENT

Helping engineers develop on Slack's platform!

Slack — Customer Experience Agent, Senior Customer Experience Agent

JUNE 2016 - AUGUST 2018, AUGUST 2018 - JULY 2020

Empathising and communicating with customers in a timely, thoughtful, considerate manner. Identifying and documenting bugs for the Engineering teams, and working alongside Product and QA to test, troubleshoot, and provide feedback. Sharing knowledge and learnings with the team. Developing new processes and tools.

Fortress Information Systems — Technical Support Coordinator

AUGUST 2013 - JUNE 2016

Guiding and assisting customers with their use of venue and event ticketing software. Building, querying, testing and optimising databases (SQL). Infrastructure management. Troubleshooting and problem solving hardware and software issues. Training new team members and documenting knowledge.

Decision Intellect — Client Services Advisor

DECEMBER 2012 - JUNE 2013

Supporting, maintaining and training of credit-decisioning software.

EDUCATION

University of Otago Bachelor of Science (BSc), Computer Science 2007 - 2012

300 level papers, including: Effective Programming, Database Theory and Applications, Object-Oriented Programming and Computer Graphics.

Beyond my formal education, I frequently undertake online courses via Udemy, Pluralsight, newline. Examples of the courses I have completed include:

- Learn and Understand NodeJS
- A Full Stack REACT Masterclass
- The Complete Developers Guide to MongoDB

PROFILE

I am a Customer Experience professional, passionate about solving problems at the core.

I love technology and I enjoy gaining a deep understanding of systems. I have a keen interest in programming and enjoy developing and testing software improvements and automations. In my spare time, I like to expand my knowledge by undertaking online courses and personal projects.

I am an empathetic person and a customer advocate. I am a strong collaborator and have a team-focussed mindset. I pride myself on working hard.

I love working for Slack, a company that is changing the world.

SKILLS

- Judging severity and risk
- Troubleshooting
- Collaboration
- Leadership
- Detailed
- Coach
- Communication
- Adaptable
- Strong work ethic
- JS, HTML/CSS, SQL
- Database management